[
	{
		"question": "What technology is used to record cryptocurrency transactions?",
		"options": [
			"Mining",
			"Token",
			"Digital Wallet",
			"Blockchain"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What technology is used to make telephone calls over the Internet possible?",
		"options": [
			"HTTP",
			"HTTPS",
			"TCP/IP",
			"VoIP"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "How many bytes are in a kilobyte?",
		"options": [
			"100",
			"1000",
			"1024",
			"2020"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "How many pins does a transistor have?",
		"options": [
			"One",
			"Two",
			"Three",
			"Four"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What is electric current defined as?",
		"options": [
			"Random movements of electrons in a conductor",
			"Pressure difference between two poles",
			"The power that causes drift of electrons",
			"Movement of free electrons prominently in one direction"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Who is the founder of SpaceX?",
		"options": [
			"Jeff Bezos",
			"Elon Musk",
			"Jack Ma",
			"Bob Miner"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which company created the game Minecraft?",
		"options": [
			"Sony",
			"Nintendo",
			"Mojang Studios",
			"Tencent"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Who created the first web page?",
		"options": [
			"Tim Berners-Lee",
			"Tim Cook",
			"Bjarne Stroustrup",
			"Guido Van Rossum"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Who invented the MRI machine?",
		"options": [
			"Thomas Jefferson",
			"Johannes Gutenberg",
			"Wilhelm Conrad RÃ¶ntgen",
			"Raymond Damadian"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is Google's parent company?",
		"options": [
			"Alphabet Inc.",
			"Meta",
			"Intel Corporation",
			"Boeing Company"
		],
		"answer": 0
	}
]